http://www.patol.co.uk/cookies-privacy-policy

Patol
T: +44 (0) 118 9701 701   E: info@patol.uk.com
HomeAbout Patol— E, H & S Policy— AccreditationsProducts & Services— Linear Heat Detection—— Digital Cable (Non Resettable)—— Analogue Cable (Resettable)—— Fibresense Linear Temperature Sensing (LTS)—— ADW Tube-Type LHD— Infrared Transit (Conveyor) Heat & Flame Sensors— Special Fire & Safety Control Equipment & Services— Aspirating Smoke Detectors—— ASD 535—— ASD 532—— ASD 531—— Pipes & Fittings— Thermal Imaging Heat Detection—— FireTIR System—— FeverTIR SystemIndustries— Fire Safety for Conveyors — Fire Safety in Cable Tunnels, Risers and Flats— Fire Safety in Storage Tanks— Fire Safety in Recycling Plants— Fire Safety in Car Parks— Fire Safety in Road Tunnels— Fire Safety in the Food Industry— Fire Safety in EscalatorsTechnical Library— Analogue LHDC—— Information Sheets—— Data Sheets—— Installation Guides—— Approvals—— Consultant Specifications— Analogue LHDC Controllers—— Information Sheets—— Data Sheets—— Installation Guides—— Approvals—— Drawings—— Legacy— Digital LHDC—— Information Sheets—— Data Sheets—— Installation Guides—— Approvals—— Consultant Specifications— Digital LHDC Controllers—— Information Sheets—— Data Sheets—— Approvals— Fibresense Linear Temperature Sensing (LTS)—— Information Sheets—— Manuals—— Approvals— Infrared Transit Heat Sensors—— Information Sheets—— Data Sheets—— Manuals—— Approvals—— Drawings—— Legacy—— Consultant Specifications— Infrared Transit Flame Sensors—— Information Sheets—— Manuals— Special Control Equipment—— Information Sheets—— Legacy— Applications—— Guides— Aspirating Smoke Detection—— Information Sheets— Thermal Imaging Heat Detection—— Information SheetsPressContact Us
HomeAbout Patol
E, H & S PolicyAccreditations
Products & Services
Linear Heat Detection
Digital Cable (Non Resettable)Analogue Cable (Resettable)Fibresense Linear Temperature Sensing (LTS)ADW Tube-Type LHD
Infrared Transit (Conveyor) Heat & Flame SensorsSpecial Fire & Safety Control Equipment & ServicesAspirating Smoke Detectors
ASD 535ASD 532ASD 531Pipes & Fittings
Thermal Imaging Heat Detection
FireTIR SystemFeverTIR System
Industries
Fire Safety for Conveyors Fire Safety in Cable Tunnels, Risers and FlatsFire Safety in Storage TanksFire Safety in Recycling PlantsFire Safety in Car ParksFire Safety in Road TunnelsFire Safety in the Food IndustryFire Safety in Escalators
Technical Library
Analogue LHDC
Information SheetsData SheetsInstallation GuidesApprovalsConsultant Specifications
Analogue LHDC Controllers
Information SheetsData SheetsInstallation GuidesApprovalsDrawingsLegacy
Digital LHDC
Information SheetsData SheetsInstallation GuidesApprovalsConsultant Specifications
Digital LHDC Controllers
Information SheetsData SheetsApprovals
Fibresense Linear Temperature Sensing (LTS)
Information SheetsManualsApprovals
Infrared Transit Heat Sensors
Information SheetsData SheetsManualsApprovalsDrawingsLegacyConsultant Specifications
Infrared Transit Flame Sensors
Information SheetsManuals
Special Control Equipment
Information SheetsLegacy
Applications
Guides
Aspirating Smoke Detection
Information Sheets
Thermal Imaging Heat Detection
Information Sheets
PressContact Us
Home / Cookies & Privacy Policy
Personal Information
We collect Personal Information when you knowingly provide it, including when you register for the newsletter, contact us, or request information. Personal Information is information that may be used to identify or locate an individual, like a person’s full name, postal address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with this Personal Information. We use your Personal Information to send communications, to respond to your enquiries, and to send marketing and promotional messages.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information automatically when you visit our Site. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that is not used nor intended to be used to personally identify an individual and is not associated with nor linked to Personal Information. This Non-Personally Identifiable Information we collect via the Site includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and the web page you have visited immediately prior to visiting the Site.
Patol Limited will make no attempt to track or identify individual users, except where there is a reasonable suspicion that unauthorised access to systems is being attempted. In the case of all users, Patol Limited reserves the right to attempt to identify and track any individual who is reasonably suspected of trying to gain unauthorised access to computer systems or resources operating as part of Patol Limited's web services.
As a condition of use of this site, all users must give permission for Patol Limited to use its access logs to attempt to track users who are reasonably suspected of gaining, or attempting to gain, unauthorised access.
All log file information collected by Patol Limited is kept secure and no access to raw log files is given to any third party.
How we use Cookies
Cookies are small text files stored on your computer when you visit websites. We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience.
There are two ‘flavours’ of Cookies - ‘Session’ cookies and ‘Persistent’ cookies.
Session cookies are temporary and are deleted when you shut down your Web browser or turn off your computer. These are used to improve how you navigate through a website.
‘Persistent’ cookies remain on your computer until manually deleted or when they reach an expiry date. They hold information that is useful if you revisit the website, such as contact form details previosuly submitted.
You can disable cookies already stored on your computer, but this may stop our website and others from functioning properly. It may also cause saved login details, for example, to be deleted, so ensure you have a note of them before deleting all cookies.
Essential Cookies
The following is strictly necessary in the operation of our website. If you choose to allow them, cookies placed on your computer by our website will, where applicable:
'The Cookie' which allows you to access the Technical Library for up to 365 days without having to re-enter your details.
Non-essential Cookies
The following are not strictly necessary but are required to provide you with the best user experience and tell us, anonymously, which pages people find most interesting.
Functional Cookies
Typically used for tracking the pages you visit. Page tracking data is collated by Google on behalf of millions of website owners, providing anonymous data on which pages you visited, how you got there, the page you exited the website from and so on. It allows us to see which pages are more or less popular and helps us to make our website even better.
Targeting Cookies
These allow you, for example, to share pages with social networks such as Facebook (where applicable).
Data Sharing Policy
This website will not share any personal information with third parties.
The table below explains the cookies we use and why
_utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmz
Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to monitor traffic levels, search queries and visits to this website.
Google Analytics stores IP address anonymously on its servers in the US, and neither CIVIC or Google associate your IP address with any personally identifiable information.
These cookies enable Google to determine whether you are a return visitor to the site, and to track the pages that you visit during your session.
cc_social, cc_analytics
Cookie Control: The cookie tool on this website remembers your privacy settings for the next time you visit the website. The cookie stores your preferences for both Social Media and Google Analytics Cookies.
_twitter_sess, Guest_id, k, orginal_referer
Twitter module. Holds no personal data. Allows Twitter to interact with this website.
datr, a_user, a_xs
Facebook user cookie. Allows Facebook to interact with this website.
the_cookie
Allows you to access the Technical Library for up to 365 days without having to re-enter your details.
Applications
Power GenerationPetro-ChemicalWaste Recycling PlantsCar Parks Road TunnelsFood Production
Fire Safety In Escalators
Products & Services
Linear Heat DetectionInfrared Transit (Conveyor) Heat & Flame SensorsSpecial Fire & Safety Control Equipment & ServicesAspirating Smoke DetectionThermal Imaging Heat Detection
Technical Library
Analogue LHDCAnalogue LHDC ControllersDigital LHDCDigital LHDC ControllersInfrared Heat DetectionApplications
About Patol
AboutE, H & S PolicyAccreditationsContact Us
Terms & Conditions of Sale
